in with the king of
stand 이상.
>> 안녕하세요. 이상준입니다. 예.
>> 전 친구야.
>> 온 거야? 아니면 네가 배고파서
주문을 한 거야.
>> 오래 땡큐.
>> 예. 옛날부터 이제 영어를 배우고
싶은 생각이 있어서 오늘 여기까지
이렇게 출연하게 됐습니다. 예. 아
너무나 영광입니다.
>> Why are you studying
English?
>> My dream is to do
아메리카.
prepared some
missions for him to
[음악] practice his
wings
[웃음]
you here
>> are you ready
what are you doing
first we going to go
to a caf let's go
explain this place
let's go let's go
today you must order
coffee
and [음악]
prayor
can
>> 저 영어 이거밖에 안 배웠어요.
아
what
is the cake your
cake
>> 오케 아이스카페라한테
>> 디카페인트
your mission is very
difficult [웃음] do
you have a boyfriend
i think you don't
have boyfriend
because you verycky
[웃음] what si small
medum small medum
large
오케
>> 아이스 마라떼
>> 아이스
아이스카페라떼
오케이 세임
오토 오토 아이스 아메리카노 오케이
>> 예 from코리아브라
>> 예
>> can I
>> 야
>> I want to
[음악] eat
Yes.
스크스타
>> 아 it looks like very
sweet [음악]
>> right
is number one
the rasberry one
>> 오케이 one r라즈베리
>> 아이스 아메리카노 아이스 아메리카노라
>> 야 야 and 아이스카페라
디카페인
오트
>> [음악]
>> 시불시야
[음악]
>> 아 오케이 [음악]
아 영어 어렵네 일시불이 영어로
>> 아 땡큐
이거 [음악] 제가 가지러오는
거예요. 갖다 주는 거예요.
Will you bring it to
my table?
>> 아, will you?
I come get it.
>> 아, should I come get
it? 아하. 오케이. 오케이.
>> [웃음]
>> 브라질
브라질
[웃음]
거
small
>> me빅토크
[웃음]
>> thank you for
drinking coffee
>> enjoy your cof
>> enjoy your c피e
>> 와우
음. But I think this
is not oat milk. No,
I order. I order.
Can you try again?
Try again. Change
your [웃음] mouse.
Delicious. Very
delicious. How was
your comedy tour?
>> 저번에 뉴욕에서 했는데 재밌게
봐주셔서 또 가게 되었어요. LA,
애틀란 뉴욕 again. Wasc스.
Where is
>> 카고?
>> 아, 시카고. 오. [음악]
오. 시카고. I trying
study English more
and more. So I can
[음악] speak English
to performing USA
global
my dream. You can do
it. Yeah. My dream
really you're gna
talk to people on
the street. Street.
[음악]
Yes. Stranger. First
mission you have to
compliment a
stranger. I like
your shoes. I like
your hat. Wow. I
like your [음악] hair.
Recommend a
restaurant in EP.
Can you recommend
any last mission
learning English can
youach me engish?
[음악]
Let's go. Let's go.
>> Thank you.
>> I don't like a man.
[웃음] I like a girl.
>> Thank you very much.
>> Maybe that girl over
there.
>> Yeah.
>> It's a girl. So be
careful.
>> 오케이. 오케이. 오케이.
야. Excuse me. I like
your sunlass I like
your sunglass
can you recommend
good restant around
here? Do you know my
first time here?
>> 아 time are you
alone?
Travel
to예타
>> 아야 땡큐 야 아 근데 뭘 하는지 못
알아듣겠어요 제가 얘기는 했는데
얘기는 못 알아들었어 are you
al
why
can I talk about you
can speak English
but try
>> 아무도 맞잖아요 괜찮아 아, 한국말할
줄 알면 안 되지 않아요.
아 뭐로코ation
>> can you teach me in
engish we are not
we have sleep
[웃음]
comed코 [웃음]
can you teach
My friend
my friend Ick
know
how you feel meant
[웃음]
here
Don't
[웃음]
>> 뭐 한 거예요? 아 어지러워요. 뭐뭐
뭐라고 하지?
>> 노았다. 노
>> 노이 뭐야?
장난 아니고 뭐 이런
crispy por
taco
up
from
I love
I have been there
from Korea
>> I will perform in
>> august
you have Instagram
my show Instagram
show
>> how do I find you
can I try
tomorrow
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
So your mission here
is to make a friend
and you must [음악]
make them laugh and
you must ask
together.
Easy. I think so.
That was good
practice. Let's go.
You got
>> this 야
>> 바이바이.
야 오픈
>> 오픈.
>> 아 오케이 땡큐.
Welcome to the crack
your name my name
you
been ir first time
first time first
time where are from
>> 아
fr
오 do you haveil
one is good if you
want try something
little ir here reg
>> [웃음]
>> Can you one
be what brings you
hereore? First I
came to visit my
cousin Korean. No,
IR Yeah. He was here
and I visit here for
one month. But that
was years ago. [웃음]
I'm still here. It
was a long month.
Yeah. Yeah. Long
month. Are you
marry? Yes. Here.
Korean. Yes. Wow.
Thank you. This is a
Guinness. Yeah. It's
a most important
wow. Liquid in
Ireland. Do you want
to play game? Oh,
yeah. Yeah. Do you
see this black line?
You have to drink
maybe three big
drinks. And if you
finish black line on
the middle of the G,
you win a free shot.
Shot. Let go.
[웃음]
>> Are you happy?
아, 하고 싶은 말이 있는데 영어가
안 되니까 이게 영어로 하기가
힘드네.
America
>> been to America many
time.
>> You been to New
York. Oh, I last
week I was in
Tennessee with your
wife. I visit my
mom. We went to a
concert. Who?
>> Yes.
>> I can play it. I
play it for you.
Thank you very much.
You are very kind. I
love you. I want
marry you. If you
divce, I want you.
아, I know. I know
this very famous.
>> I love this love
you.
[웃음]
>> 선생님, 나 못 하겠어요.
>> 영어를 모르니까 빌드업을 할 수가
없어요. 어떻게 해야 돼요?
are best
me
[웃음]
>> 아 내가 집에서 상상만 했던 영어는
이것보다 훨씬 잘했는데라는 생각이
있었는데 나와서 막상 내뱉터 보니
이게 안 내뱉어지는구나라는 걸 알아서
많은 사람들이 영어를 공부하면은
집에서 쓰고 단어 외우고 이런 그런
걸 많이 할 건데 나와서 말을 해보고
들어보고 이게 경험해 보는게 훨씬 더
공부가 많이 된다는 거를 알았어요.
그리고 이제 또 옆에 또 이렇게
선생님이 한 분 있으면 더 빨리
도움이 된다는 걸 알아 가지고 오늘
너무나 좋은 경험을 했고 언젠가
만나면 영어로 대화를 할 수 있는 그
날을 기다리면서 우리 캘리 쌤과 함께
영어 공부 열심히 한번 해 봅시다.
예. 고맙습니다.
>> 예.
>> 바이. S